Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not annotated
      - O
        - Outkast - Southernplayalisticadillacmuzik, 1994; SR-22031; Outkast (Box 381)
          Catalog # 73008-24071-1; A-side Matrix # 73008-24071-SA
        - Outkast - Southernplayalisticadillacmuzik, 1994; SR-22032; Outkast; Goodie MoB (Box 381)
          Catalog # 73008-26010-1; A-side Matrix # 73008-26010-1-SA
        - Outkast - Git up, git out, 1994; SR-22033; Outkast; Goodie MoB (Box 381)
          Catalog # 73008-24086-1; A-side Matrix # 73008-24086-1-SA
        - Outlaw - V-R6; Injection, 1998; SR-22034; Outlaw (Box 381)
          Catalog # KAR012; A-side Matrix # KAR 012 A-1-1
          Kartoons
        - Outlaw Posse - Stop the negativity, 1990; SR-22035; Outlaw Posse; Kid G (Box 381)
          Catalog # GEET29; A-side Matrix # GEET 29 A1
          Gee Street
        - Outlawz - In the event of my demise; And I still love you, 2000; SR-22036; Outlawz; Red Rat; Geronimo Ji Jaga (Box 381)
          Catalog # INTR 10262-1; A-side Matrix # INTR-10262-1A
        - Outlife - What would u do…?, 1998; SR-22037; Outlife; Ren (Box 381)
          Catalog # EEMK001; A-side Matrix # EEMK-001-A
          Emporium Entertainment
        - Output - Move for me, 1983; SR-22038; Output (Box 381)
          Catalog # 4Z9 04230; A-side Matrix # 4Z9-04230-3-AB
          Tuff City
        - Outsidaz - Keep on; Done in the game, 2001; SR-22039; Outsidaz (Box 381)
          Catalog # RNOUTS1; A-side Matrix # RN OUTSIDAZ-A
          Ruffnation Records
        - Outsiderz 4 Life - Not enough, 2000; SR-22040; Outsiderz 4 Life (Box 381)
          Catalog # SPRO-13663; A-side Matrix # SPRO 7087-6-13663-1-0-A
          Blackground Entertainment
        - Outta Order - Tutti frutti jump, 1997; SR-22041; Outta Order; Benson, George; Total Kaos (Box 381)
          Catalog # PRO-A-8965; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-8965-A-SR-1
          Warner Bros. Records
        - Overland Stage - Overland Stage, 1972; SR-22042; Overland Stage (Box 381)
          Catalog # KE 31319; A-side Matrix # PAL 31319 A
        - Owens, Darnell - No more slack; For only heaven knows, 1985; SR-22043; Owens, Darnell (Box 381)
          Catalog # M 012; A-side Matrix # M012-A
          New-Tal Records
        - Owens, Robert - Love will find its way (the best of Robert Owens) (disc one), 2002; SR-22044; Owens, Robert; Fingers Inc.; Knuckles, Frankie; Mr. C; Photek; Sensory Elements (Box 381)
          In same jacket as # SR-22047. quadruple album.
          Catalog # USEXLP 002; A-side Matrix # USEXLP 002 A
          Unisex
        - Owens, Robert - Love will find its way (the best of Robert Owens) (disc two), 2002; SR-22045; Owens, Robert; Fingers Inc.; Knuckles, Frankie; Mr. C; Photek; Sensory Elements (Box 381)
          In same jacket as # SR-22046. quadruple album.
          Catalog # USEXLP 002; A-side Matrix # USEXLP 002 C
        - Owens, Robert - Love will find its way (the best of Robert Owens) (disc three), 2002; SR-22046; Owens, Robert; Fingers Inc.; Knuckles, Frankie; Mr. C; Photek; Sensory Elements (Box 381)
          In same jacket as # SR-22045. quadruple album.
          Catalog # USEXLP 002; A-side Matrix # USEXLP 002 E
        - Owens, Robert - Love will find its way (the best of Robert Owens) (disc four), 2002; SR-22047; Owens, Robert; Fingers Inc.; Knuckles, Frankie; Mr. C; Photek; Sensory Elements (Box 381)
          In same jacket as # SR-22044. quadruple album.
          Catalog # USEXLP 002; A-side Matrix # USEXLP 002 G
        - Owens, Robert - Far away; Happy, 1990; SR-22048; Owens, Robert; Knuckles, Frankie (Box 381)
          Catalog # 440 514-0 DJ; A-side Matrix # 162 440 514-O-A-SP
          4th & Broadway
        - Oxa, Anna - Pensami per te, 1988; SR-22049; Oxa, Anna (Box 381)
          Catalog # CBS 460665 1; A-side Matrix # C1460665-1-1L-27-1-88
          CBS
          Milan, Italy
        - OXO - Whirly girl, 1983; SR-22050; OXO (Box 381)
          Catalog # PRO-A-2015; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-2015-SH1
        - Oz & Storm - Street knowledge, 1998; SR-22051; Oz & Storm (Box 381)
          Catalog # FM008; A-side Matrix # FM008-A
          Freakin' Music
          West Palm Beach, Florida
        - Ock, Mike - Day in the life, 1998; SR-22052; Ock, Mike (Box 381)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # GTH-01-A
          Ghost Town Records
        - Ohio Players - Pain, 1972; SR-30833; Ohio Players (Box 376)
          Catalog # WB 2015; A-side Matrix # WB-2015-A
          Westbound Records
        - Ohio Players - Graduation, 1984; SR-30834; Ohio Players (Box 376)
          Catalog # A-403-OP-LP; A-side Matrix # 405079X-A
          Air City Records
          Dayton, Ohio
        - Ohio Players - Graduation, 1984; SR-30835; Ohio Players (Box 376)
        - Oingo Boingo - Private life; Whole day off; Nothing to fear; Grey matter, 1982; SR-30836; Oingo Boingo (Box 376)
          Catalog # SP-17203; A-side Matrix # A+M-SP-017203-A-(RE-1) T1
        - Omar - Mr. Postman, 1985; SR-30837; Omar (Box 376)
          Catalog # DPS 002; A-side Matrix # DPS-002-A1
          London, England
        - One And One - Phenomenon, 1996; SR-30838; One And One (Box 376)
          Catalog # NPE 1440; A-side Matrix # NPE-1440-1 A
          Next Plateau Entertainment
        - OnePhatDeeva- Bad habit (remixes), 2000; SR-30839; OnePhatDeeva; ATFC (Box 376)
          Catalog # DFECT19DJ5; A-side Matrix # 08 44695 20 1A1 DFECT 19 DJ5
          Defected
        - Optical - Moving 808s; High tek dreams, 1997; SR-30840; Optical (Box 376)
          Catalog # PRO 009; A-side Matrix # PRO-009 A1
          Prototype Recordings
          England
        - Osborne & Giles - Stranger in the night, 1985; SR-30841; Osborne & Giles (Box 376)
          Catalog # V-70050; A-side Matrix # V+70050-A F-1
        - Otierre and La Pina - Dalla sede (basi strumentali) (Disc one), 1997; SR-25358; Otierre; La Pina (Box 376)
          In same jacket as # SR-25359; SR-25360; SR-25361. Double album, 2 copies.
          Catalog # 5002 379; A-side Matrix # 5002379 1 1 5 20
        - Otierre and La Pina - Dalla sede (basi strumentali) (Disc two), 1997; SR-25359; Otierre; La Pina (Box 376)
          In same jacket as # SR-25358; SR-25360; SR-25361. Double album, 2 copies.
          Catalog # 5002 379; A-side Matrix # 5002379 2 1 5 20
        - Otierre and La Pina - Dalla sede (basi strumentali) (Disc one), 1997; SR-25360; Otierre; La Pina (Box 376)
          In same jacket as # SR-25358; SR-25359; SR-25361. Double album, 2 copies.
        - Otierre and La Pina - Dalla sede (basi strumentali) (Disc two), 1997; SR-25361; Otierre; La Pina (Box 376)
          In same jacket as # SR-25358; SR-25359; SR-25360. Double album, 2 copies.